I'm going to show you exactly how you
我将向你展示如何
can start making better AI characters
才能制作出
than 99% of people because after testing
比 99% 的人都更好的 AI 角色，因为在测试了
pretty much every method out there to
几乎所有
create consistent characters, the same
创建一致角色的方法之后，同样的
problems kept coming up over and over
问题反复出现
again. Yes, we have a ton of AI tools
。 是的，我们现在有很多人工智能工具
right now that can generate and edit
可以生成和编辑
images and technically they can give you
图像，从技术上讲，它们可以提供相当
a decent level of consistency, but in
不错的图像一致性，但
reality it just doesn't work as good as
实际上它们的效果远不如
it sounds. You're stuck hunting for that
听起来那么好。 你还在苦苦寻找那张
one perfect reference image. Then you
完美的参考图片。 然后，
tool every single time you want to
每次你想
create something new and the moment you
创作新作品时，都必须将素材重新输入到工具中；而一旦你
want to change anything like the pose,
想改变姿势、
clothing, or the environment, you're
服装或环境等任何内容，就必须
back to re-explaining which image to use
重新解释要使用哪张图片
and how to use it. It works, but it's
以及如何使用它。 它确实有效，但很
annoying. And I'm not even mentioning
烦人。 我甚至还没提到把
multiple characters in the same scene.
多个角色放在同一个场景中会发生什么。
That's a whole other nightmare. But
那简直是另一场噩梦。 但是，在
after all this time struggling with
尝试了
those other methods, I came across an
这么多其他方法之后，我发现了一个
update that completely changed the way
更新，它彻底改变了
this whole setup works. It made
整个设置的工作方式。 它使创建
consistent characters by far the easiest
一致的角色变得
and most efficient they've ever been. So
前所未有的简单高效。 所以
in this video, I'm going to show you how
在这个视频中，我将向你展示如何
to create consistent characters from
从零开始创建一致的角色
scratch, how to create multiple of them,
，如何创建多个角色，
and make them interact across images in
以及如何以最简单的方式让它们在图像之间进行交互
the easiest way possible. And finally,
。 最后，
we will take all of that and turn it
我们将把所有这些素材制作
into a realistic high-quality AI video.
成逼真的高质量人工智能视频。
Now, the tool we are going to be using
现在，我们将使用名为 OpenArt 的工具
to create our consistent characters is
来创建我们统一的角色
called OpenArt. The reason we are using
。 我们使用
OpenArt is because they just updated
OpenArt 的原因是他们刚刚更新了
their character feature and made it
角色功能，使其性能
significantly better. Among the things
显著提升。
they updated is a way easier to use and
他们更新的内容包括更易于使用和
navigate interface, much better training
导航的界面、更好的
for your characters, the ability to
角色训练、
freely select the models you are using
自由选择所用模型的功能
and resolution that goes as high as 4K
以及高达 4K 的分辨率等等
amongst tons and tons of other features.
。
This means you now have full control
这意味着你现在可以完全控制
over how your characters look and behave
角色
across different generations without the
在不同世代中的外观和行为，而不受
usual limitations. So with that being
以往的限制。 那么
said, let's jump right into the main
，接下来我们就直接进入主
interface. And if you want to follow
界面吧。 如果你想跟着
along with this tutorial, I have left a
这个教程一起学习，我在
link to OpenArt down below. Once inside
下面留下了 OpenArt 的链接。 进入
the main interface, we want to go ahead
主界面后，我们
and click over to the left where it says
点击左侧写着“
character. Here you will find your main
角色”的地方。 这里是你的
character dashboard. If you already have
主角仪表盘。 如果您已经
characters in OpenArt, you are actually
在 OpenArt 中拥有角色，您
able to upgrade any of those to this new
可以将其中任何角色升级到此新
version. But if you do not have any, you
版本。 但如果你没有任何账户，你
can create one in two different ways.
可以通过两种不同的方式创建一个。
The first option is to start with an
第一种方法是从一张
image. Here you are prompted to upload
图片开始。 这里提示您上传
between one and four images. One that is
一到四张图片。 其中一项是
required and three extra that will help
必需的，另外三项是额外的，可以帮助
the model better understand your
模型从不同角度更好地理解你的
character from different angles. The
性格。
second option is to start with a
第二种方法是先进行
description. Here you can just write the
描述。 在这里，您可以直接输入
exact prompt of your character and
角色的具体描述，并
select the model that it will use.
选择它将使用的模型。
OpenArt's default model is going to be
OpenArt 的默认模型将沿用
the one that was used in the previous
上一版本中使用的模型
version. This one just allows you to use
。 这个工具允许你使用
different styles like photorealistic,
不同的风格，例如照片写实风格、
digital art, anime, 3D, Pixar, fantasy,
数字艺术风格、动漫风格、3D风格、皮克斯风格、奇幻风格
and RPG. Or you can select any of the
和角色扮演风格。 或者您可以选择其他任何
other top models out there and you will
热门型号，并且
still have the option to create them in
仍然可以选择以
different styles. This gives you a lot
不同的风格创建它们。 这让你拥有
more flexibility depending on the type
更大的灵活性，具体取决于
of content you are creating. So let's go
你创建的内容类型。 那么，让我们来
ahead and test out NanoBanana Pro. This
测试一下 NanoBanana Pro 吧。
is the model that I think works the
我认为这是效果
best. I'm going to write this prompt
最好的模式。 我打算在这里写下这个提示：
right here, a natural portrait shot of
拍摄
an Asian woman in her 20s. She looks
一位20多岁亚洲女性的自然肖像照。 她看起来
like a 20-year-old Gen Z influencer,
像个20岁的Z世代网红，
beautiful, natural looking with
漂亮自然，而且有
professional studio lighting. Once we
专业的影棚灯光。
have everything here, we want to go
一切准备就绪后，我们就可以开始
ahead and select our style. I am going
选择款式了。
to go with photorealistic for this one
这次我打算选择照片级写实风格，
and then I am going to click generate.
然后点击生成。
OpenArt will give us four different
OpenArt 会给我们提供四个不同
versions of our character and we can
版本的角色，我们可以
select the one that we like the best or
选择最喜欢的一个，或者
regenerate them if none of them feel
如果都不满意，也可以重新生成角色
right. But I am actually happy with the
。 但我其实对
one in the top left, so I am going to go
左上角的那个很满意，所以我打算
ahead and click that one and click on
点击它，然后点击“
build my character. Once that is done,
创建我的角色”。 完成后，
it is going to give us four different
它会给我们提供四张不同的
images so that we can see the results
图像，以便我们可以看到
the model is going to be trained on.
模型将要训练的结果。
These are the front view, the close-up
这些分别是正面图、特写
view, the full body view, and the back
图、全身图和背面
view. This is important because it
图。 这一点很重要，因为它能
ensures your character stays consistent
确保你的角色
from every angle, which is exactly what
从各个角度都保持一致，这正是
you need when placing them in different
你之后将他们置于不同
scenes later. Once they are all
场景时所需要的。 全部
generated, you have the option to either
生成后，您可以选择
regenerate all of them or just
重新生成所有文件，或者只
regenerate the ones you are not happy
重新生成您不满意的文件
with. And once everything looks good,
。 一切看起来都不错之后，
you want to go ahead and click looks
你就可以点击“看起来
good. Finally, you want to add a name
不错”了。 最后，你需要
and a backstory to your character. The
为你的角色添加名字和背景故事。
backstory is optional, but I recommend
背景故事是可选的，但
adding it if you have the time. It will
如果你有时间，我建议添加。 这将为
give the AI more context about who the
人工智能提供更多关于
character is and it will be able to
角色背景的信息，使其能够
generate images that better fit what you
生成更符合你
have imagined. I'm going to call mine
想象的图像。 我打算给我的角色取名叫罗宾，以下是它的
Robin and write this for the backstory.
背景故事。
Robin is a 20-year-old influencer. She
罗宾是一位20岁的网红。 她
is very interested in sports and skiing
对运动和滑雪非常感兴趣，
and is really passionate about that. She
并且充满热情。 她
doesn't have a lot of personal life and
几乎没有个人生活，把
she dedicates a lot of it to her skiing
大部分时间都投入到了滑雪
career. Then click here and this will
事业中。 然后点击这里，即可
save your character ready for you to
保存您的角色信息，供您
use. Now, before we jump into the actual
使用。 现在，在我们正式进入角色
generation interface, I'm going to go
生成界面之前，我将
ahead and create another character. But
先创建另一个角色。 但
this time I am going to start with an
这次我打算用
image instead of a description. I
图片而不是文字描述来开头。 我
actually have four images prepared, so I
其实准备了四张图片，所以我
will upload my primary image right here.
会在这里上传我的主图。
Then I am going to upload an image of
然后我将上传一张
her looking slightly towards the left,
她略微向左看的照片，
one looking towards the right, and
一张她向右看的照片，
finally an image of her from the back.
最后上传一张她的背影照。
Finally, I'll call her Leila and give
最后，我给她取名为莱拉，并给
her a short backstory. The reason I am
她简单介绍一下背景故事。 我之所以要
creating a second character is that
创建第二个角色
later on, we are going to make them
，是因为之后我们要让他们
interact with each other inside the same
在同一个
scene. So now we have both of our
场景中互动。 现在我们已经
characters generated. Let's jump into
生成了两个角色。 让我们进入
our first character and check out the
第一个角色，看看
interface. To do that, you want to click
界面。 要做到这一点，你需要
on this button that says create and here
点击“创建”按钮，然后
you will have the full interface
你就可以看到完整的界面了
available to you. At the top, this is
。 在顶部，
where you can select or switch between
您可以在这里选择或切换
your characters. And if you click on add
角色。 如果您点击“添加
character, this is where you will be
角色”，您就
able to add your other characters as
可以在这里添加其他角色
well, which is what we will do in just a
，我们马上就会这样做
moment. Next up, you have the prompt
。 接下来是提示
section and this is probably the most
部分，这可能是其中最
useful part in here. This is where you
有用的部分。 在这里，你可以
describe what you want your character to
描述你希望你的角色在
be doing, where they are, and what they
做什么，他们在哪里，以及他们
are wearing. Below that, you have the
穿着什么。 下方您可以
option to upload reference images. And
选择上传参考图片。
the coolest thing is that whenever you
最酷的是，每当你
reference them in your prompt, it will
在提示中引用它们时，它
actually bring up the entire image and
实际上都会显示整个图像，
you will be able to tag it directly. I
你可以直接给它添加标签。 我马上就给
will show you exactly how this works in
你演示一下它的工作原理
just a second. Then you have the output
。 然后您可以
size selection, so you can choose
选择输出尺寸，因此您可以选择
between various different output sizes
各种不同的输出尺寸，
and go as high as 4K resolution. This is
最高可达 4K 分辨率。
great if you are creating content for
如果您正在为
platforms that require high-quality
需要高质量
visuals or if you just want your images
视觉效果的平台创建内容，或者您​​只是想让您的图像
to look as sharp as possible. And
看起来尽可能清晰，那么这非常棒。
finally, you have the ability to select
最后，您可以选择
whatever model you prefer to use,
使用您喜欢的任何型号，
whether it is NanoBanana Pro,
无论是 NanoBanana Pro、
NanoBanana, or SeaDream. But I usually
NanoBanana 还是 SeaDream。 但我通常
just leave it on auto so that the AI can
都把它设置成自动模式，让人工智能
decide for itself what model works best
自己决定哪种模型最适合
for the prompt. Okay, so now you know
提示信息。 好了，现在你知道
how the entire interface works. Let us
整个界面是如何运作的了。 让我们开始
go ahead and generate our first image.
生成第一张图像吧。
But quickly before that, I am going to
但在此之前，我要
click on add character and add the
点击“添加角色”，添加
second character that I created, which
我创建的第二个角色，也
is Leila. Now I have both Robin and
就是莱拉。 现在罗宾和
Leila ready to use. For the prompt, I'm
莱拉都准备好了，可以使用了。 对于提示，我
going to start off by writing at Robin
将从第一张图片中罗宾
and at Leila at the ski center standing
和莱拉站在滑雪中心
on the top of the ski mountain at image
山顶的场景开始写作
number one. And here I have this image
。 这里有一张
of the ski center that I want them to be
滑雪中心的图片，我想让他们去那里
at, so I will upload that as image
，所以我会把它上传为第一张图片
number one. They are posing for a photo
。 他们正在一起摆姿势拍照
together. Then I also want to give them
。 然后我还想给他们
two different outfits. So I am going to
两套不同的衣服。 所以我
write at Robin is wearing this ski
要写“罗宾穿着这套滑雪
outfit and then I am going to attach
服”，然后我要把
this image right here and write at image
这张图片附在这里，并写“图片
two. Then I am going to write while at
二”。 然后，我打算在
Leila is wearing this one and attach a
Leila 穿着这件衣服的时候写点什么，并附上一张
new image and write at image three. Now
新图片，然后在第三张图片上写点什么。 现在
I'm going to select 4K for quality and
我选择 4K 画质，然后
click generate and there we go. We have
点击生成，搞定！ 我们有
four images with our characters staying
四张图片，图片中人物形象
perfectly intact wearing the exact
完好无损，穿着
outfits that we gave them and we
我们给他们设计的服装，而我们
literally made this in seconds. This is
真的只用了几秒钟就完成了。 这简直
insanely cool and a really good result
太酷了，效果也非常好，
not only because of the quality, but
不仅因为质量好，
also because of how easy this was to
还因为它使用起来非常方便
use. You did not have to re-explain who
。 你无需重新解释
the characters are. You did not have to
角色是谁。 你不需要
paste in reference images over and over
一遍又一遍地粘贴参考图片
again. You just tagged them, described
。 你只需给他们贴上标签，描述
what you wanted, and it worked. But if
你想要的东西，就成功了。 但如果
you thought that this is the extent of
你认为这就是
the character tool inside OpenArt, you
OpenArt 中角色工具的全部功能，那就
are very much mistaken. For this next
大错特错了。 接下来这个
example, I am going to quickly remove
例子，我将快速移除
Leila and just work with Robin. I am
Leila，只保留 Robin。 我要
going to write this prompt. Robin is
写下这个提示。 罗宾
speed wearing this outfit and in this
穿着这身衣服，摆着这个
pose right here. She is going extremely
姿势，正高速滑下滑雪山。 她速度非常
fast and the wind is hitting her face,
快，风吹得她脸颊生疼，
but she is nevertheless happy. The
但她依然很开心。
weather outside is sunny. Now I'm going
外面阳光明媚。 现在我要
to attach the image for the outfit. It
附上这套服装的图片。
is going to be the same pink ski outfit
还是之前那套粉色滑雪服
from before. But for the pose, I want to
。 但是，在姿势上，我想
do something different. I am going to
尝试一些不同的东西。 我将
click on one of the image fields and
点击其中一个图像字段，然后在
here I am going to click on 3D editor.
这里点击 3D 编辑器。
This will bring up a 3D editor that we
这将打开一个 3D 编辑器，我们
can now use to change the position of
现在可以使用它来改变
our character. You can move and adjust
角色的位置。 您可以随意移动和调整
the body however you like and it is
身体，它会
going to very closely replicate that
非常精确地复制该
exact pose to create an image that looks
姿势，从而创建出看起来
super realistic. This means you are no
超级逼真的图像。 这意味着你
longer limited to whatever poses you can
不再局限于网上能找到的各种姿势
find online. You can create exactly what
。 你可以完全按照
you have in mind. So I am going to start
自己的想法来创作。 所以我首先要从
from the pose library. Then I am going
姿势库中选择冲刺动画。 然后我要
to turn the camera slightly around,
稍微转动一下摄像机，
bring the second leg up, and the arm
抬起她的第二条腿，
down so that she looks like she is in
放下她的手臂，让她看起来像是
going down on her skis. The next thing
蹲着滑雪一样。 接下来，
you want to do is position your camera
你需要做的就是将相机摆放到
in the exact way that you want the photo
你想要拍摄照片的确切位置
to be taken from. This is going to be
。
really closely replicated in the final
最终图像将非常精确地还原这一点
image, so take your time and position
，所以请慢慢来，把
the camera exactly how you want it. And
相机摆放到你想要的位置。
when everything looks perfect, you want
当一切看起来都很完美时，你需要
to click update pose. This will
点击更新姿势。 这样就能
instantly save it and bring it up as a
立即保存并将其作为
reference image. Now as you probably
参考图像显示出来。 正如你可能已经
saw, there is a lot of customization
看到的，这里有很多自定义选项
here. You can select different body
。 您可以选择不同的
types, different genders, and different
体型、不同的性别和不同的
pre-made poses. So you can use this for
预设姿势。 所以你可以用它来做
a lot of different things and really get
很多不同的事情，并且能够
the positioning right on whatever
准确地定位
character you are working with. But with
你所处理的任何角色。 但是，话虽如此
that said, let us go ahead and reference
，我们还是继续
our 3D image in the prompt. I am going
在提示中引用我们的 3D 图像吧。 我要
to make sure everything is good and here
确保一切顺利，而且
I actually want to use the NanoBanana
我特意想使用 NanoBanana
Pro model specifically because I want
Pro 型号，因为我希望
this image to turn out really good. So I
这张照片能拍得非常好。 所以我
am going to switch it from auto to
打算把它从自动模式切换到
NanoBanana Pro. Then I am going to click
NanoBanana Pro 模式。 然后我点击
create and here is the result. You can
创建，结果如下。 你可以
clearly see that the image that came out
清楚地看到，生成的图像与
matches the position we set our
我们设定的角色姿势完全吻合
character in. The pose is exactly what
。姿势与
we created in the 3D editor, the
我们在3D编辑器中创建的完全一致，
character looks consistent, and the
角色看起来也很协调，
overall image is looking really good.
整体图像效果非常好。
Now the final cool feature I want to
现在我要向大家展示的最后一个很棒的功能
show you inside here is the position
是定位
feature. For the prompt, I am going to
功能。 根据提示，我将
write Robin is skating on an empty
写罗宾
frozen lake alone in this exact place.
独自一人在这个地方的空旷冰冻湖面上滑冰。
She is wearing winter clothes. For the
她穿着冬装。 至于
image, I am going to click on position
图片，我将点击位置，
and upload an image of this empty frozen
上传一张我眼前这张空旷冰冻
lake that I have right here. Once the
湖面的图片。
image is uploaded, you will get this
图片上传后，会
little square showing up and you can
出现一个小方框，您可以将
move it freely across the entire image.
其在整个图片上自由移动。
You can also change how small or big it
你还可以调整它的大小
is. So if I position my rectangle right
。 所以如果我把矩形框放在
over here, this will be the exact place
这里，那么最终图像
where my character will show up in the
中我的角色就​​会出现在这个确切的位置
final image. This gives you precise
。 这可以让你精确
control over composition, which is
控制构图，
especially useful when you want your
当你想要将
character placed in a very specific part
角色放置在
of the scene. I am going to click save
场景中的特定位置时，这尤其有用。 我将点击保存
placement and this will show up as a
位置，这张图片将显示为
reference image. Then I will just
参考图像。 然后，在描述完她所在位置之后，我会
reference this image in my prompt after
在提示中引用这张图片
I have described where she is. I am
。 我
going to select NanoBanana Pro for the
将选择 NanoBanana Pro 作为
model, click create, and there you have
模型，点击创建，就完成了
it. She is in the exact same place as
。 她的位置和
where where we positioned her, still
我们之前安排的完全一样，仍然
looking like our exact character wearing
穿着冬装，看起来和我们设定的角色一模一样
winter clothes, and the image is high
，而且图像
quality and looks great. Now that we
质量很高，看起来很棒。 现在我们已经
know the basics and the most powerful
了解了 OpenArt
features of the character tool inside
中角色工具的基本原理和最强大的功能
OpenArt, let's actually create something
，让我们实际创作一些东西
and make a video out of it. For this, I
并制作一个视频吧。 为此，我
am going to take this image of our
将使用
we created earlier and use it as my
我们之前创建的人物下山的图片作为我的
starting frame. The video I want to
起始帧。 我想
create is Robin going down the mountain
制作的视频是：罗宾穿着滑雪板从山上滑下来
on her skis, then she stops, and then
，然后她停下来，接着
she looks towards the camera. And
她看向镜头。 在
throughout the whole video, she is going
整个视频中，她将始终
to stay perfectly consistent. But first,
保持完全一致。 但首先，
I need to create an end frame. So, I'm
我需要创建一个结束帧。 所以，我要
going to write this prompt. Robin is
写下这个提示。 第一张照片中，罗宾
after she just got off the mountain at
刚从山上下来，正站在滑雪道的底部
image number one. I am including the
。 我把
starting frame as a reference so that
起始帧也包含在内作为参考，以便
the AI has context of where our
人工智能能够了解我们的
character is and what she has been
角色在哪里以及她一直在
doing. This helps keep the two images
做什么。 这有助于使两幅图像
visually connected. I am also going to
在视觉上保持联系。 我还要
write super happy because I want this to
写上“超级开心”，因为我希望这段
feel like an upbeat energetic video. And
视频能给人一种积极向上、充满活力的感觉。
then finally, so that the AI does not
最后，为了避免人工智能
get inconsistent with the clothing, I'm
在服装方面出现不一致，我还要
also going to write wearing these exact
写上“穿着这些
clothes and I'm going to reattach the
衣服”，然后我会重新附上
image of her outfit and write at image
她的服装图片，并在图片
two. Now, with that done, I'm going to
二中写上。 现在，一切就绪，我要
make sure everything is set to the best
确保所有设置都达到最佳
quality. I'm going to select Nano Banana
状态。 我将选择 Nano Banana
Pro for the model, increase the number
Pro 作为模型，将图像数量增加到
of images to four, and click create. And
四张，然后单击创建。
here we have a couple of good ones. I
这里有几个不错的例子。 我
really like this one. It actually has
非常喜欢这个。 照片中
her cheeks red, which makes it look a
她的双颊泛红，看起来
little bit more natural and cold weather
更自然，也更适合寒冷的天气
appropriate. So, I'm going to go ahead
。 所以，我接下来要
and download this image. Now, we have
下载这张图片。 现在，我们已经
both of our images ready, the starting
准备好了两张图片，起始
frame and the end frame. We are going to
帧和结束帧。 我们现在要
switch over to the video mode on the
切换到左侧的视频模式
left side right here. And out of all the
。 在所有
options, we want to select image to
选项中，我们想选择图像转
video. Now, we want to make sure we
视频。 现在，我们要确保
select the correct type of model. What
选择正确的型号。
we are looking for is one that has the
我们正在寻找的是一个带有
end frame tag on it. This is important
末端框架标签的框架。 这很重要，
because it allows you to define both
因为它可以让你定义
where the video starts and where it
视频的开始和
ends, giving you much more control over
结束位置，从而让你对最终结果拥有更大的控制权
the final result. A couple of good ones
。
I can recommend are Google VO 3.1, Kling
我可以推荐几个不错的软件，分别是 Google VO 3.1、Kling
2.6, and Pixverse. All of them get solid
2.6 和 Pixverse。 它们都能
results with end frame videos. For this
通过最终帧视频获得良好的效果。 这次
one, I'm going to use Kling 2.6. I'm
我将使用 Kling 2.6。 我
going to make sure that my duration is
要确保持续时间
set to 10 seconds and that I have the
设置为 10 秒，并
best quality model selected. Then I can
选择最高质量的模型。 这样我就可以
upload both of my images. I'm going to
上传我的两张图片了。 我打算
upload the first one where our character
上传第一张图，图中我们的人物
is going down the mountain as my
正在下山，作为
starting frame and the one of her
起始帧；然后上传她
standing at the bottom as my end frame.
站在山脚下的那张图，作为结束帧。
Finally, I'm going to make sure
最后，我要检查
everything looks good, nothing is wrong,
一切是否正常，没有任何错误，
and I'm going to click create. And here
然后点击创建。
is the result. In my opinion, this video
结果如下。 我觉得这段视频
came out looking really cool. Our
拍出来效果非常酷。 我们的
character stays perfectly consistent
人物形象在整个视频中始终保持一致，
final result looks amazing. One more
最终效果非常棒。
thing you can do is have your character
你还可以将你的角色
as a reference image in the element to
作为参考图像添加到“元素到
video option. This way, you can generate
视频”选项中。 这样，你就可以直接生成
videos with your character without
包含你角色的视频，而
needing to start with an image. And you
无需从图像开始。 你
can even use them as characters in the
甚至可以将它们用作
story feature. Or you can make longer
故事功能中的角色。 或者你可以制作更长的
videos featuring your character. So, now
视频，让你的角色出场。 现在，
you know exactly how the new OpenArt
您已经完全了解了 OpenArt 新推出的
consistent character feature works and
一致性字符功能的工作原理，也
you know how to use all of its most
知道如何使用它的所有
powerful features. You can create
强大功能。 您
characters from scratch using just a
只需输入描述即可从头开始创建角色
description, add multiple characters,
，添加多个角色，
and use them simultaneously in one
并在同一张图片中同时使用它们
image. And you can take any image you
。 您可以将创建的任何图像
create and turn it into a fully
转换成完全
consistent video. What this means is
连贯的视频。 这意味着
that you no longer need to go back and
你不再需要反复
forth with your generator trying to get
与生成器沟通，才能获得
the exact positioning character right.
准确的字符定位。
You no longer have to constantly
您不再需要一遍又一遍地
regenerate the same image over and over
重新生成同一张图片，
again just to get your character to
才能让您的角色
understand whatever reference image you
理解您
included in the prompt. Because here,
在提示中包含的任何参考图片。 因为在这里，
you actually have the ability to tag
您可以
your images directly so the AI knows
直接给图片添加标签，这样人工智能就能
exactly what you are referring to in
准确地知道您在
that exact moment. And that means you
那一刻指的是什么。 这意味着在使用 AI 来创建一致的角色时，您
are getting the best possible experience
将获得最佳体验
characters. All of this is thanks to
。 这一切都要感谢
OpenArt. OpenArt is a tool that makes
OpenArt。  OpenArt 是一款能够
this feature possible and they are
实现此功能的工具，他们
constantly working on releasing the best
不断致力于
and most powerful features for creators
为像您这样的创作者发布最好、最强大的功能
like you. So, if you want to start using
。 所以，如果你想开始使用
consistent characters and create images
统一的角色，并创作出
and videos just like the ones we made
像我们今天制作的这样的图像和视频，
today, go ahead and sign up to OpenArt
那就
using my link down in the description
使用下面说明中的链接注册 OpenArt 吧，
below and I will see you guys in the
我们下期再见
next one.
。